mcjonline.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy | mcjOnline - What Is My Website Worth

**This Privacy Policy explains our information practices for the MCJ Online website.**

We want you to understand how we may use your information, before you provide it. The purpose of this policy is to inform you of what type of information (if any) we gather and track, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share that information.

**Personal Information**

You can visit MCJ Online on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself. However, you may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us information such as your name and address or e-mail ID so we may correspond with you, or provide you with subscription or other service related information. If you tell us that you do not want us to use information you provide to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect it. If you give us personal information about somebody else, we will assume that you have their prior permission to do so, because we can’t control such cases.

**Using and Sharing Personal Information  **

The following paragraphs describe in more detail how we may use the information you provide to us on the MCJ Online site and with whom we may share it. Depending on the part of the MCJ Online site you are visiting, one or more of the following paragraphs may apply:

**Fulfilling Your Request**

If you request something from or through the MCJ Online Web site (for example, more information on a product or service or a callback) we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information with others. For instance, our affiliates, business partners, financial institutions, or postal or government authorities may participate in fulfilling your request. These are very rare cases but we feel that we should let you know it before you submit personal information.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our Websites may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware that when they leave our Websites for another site, even if through a link, they should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. The provision of external links to other websites is a common practice on the Internet and it in no way indicates that we endorse or approve the linked company, or its products, services or website.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, MCJ Online makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

MCJ Online does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MCJ Online Googles use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to MCJ Online and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include but are not limited to:

  * Google Adsense
  * BuySellAds

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on MCJ Online send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

_MCJ Online has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers._

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. MCJ Onlines privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Disclosures Required By Law**

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.

**Enforcement**

MCJ Online regularly reviews its compliance with this policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this. It is our policy to contact the inquiring user regarding his or her questions.

**Changes to this Policy**

This Privacy Policy may occasionally change. Any Policy changes will be posted to this page. Each version of this policy will be denoted at the top of this page by its effective date.

_Privacy Policy last updated on October 16, 2012_
